https://www.accesscreditunion.com/privacy-notice-2/

AD&D / HAP
Identity Theft Ins.
CHECKING
All Access Access Advantage Alpha Checking MC Debit Cards Courtesy Pay Direct Deposit
SAVINGS
Deposit Rates Traditional Savings TUTMA Term Deposits Money Market IRA IRA Term Deposit Sammie Saver’s Club
BUSINESS
Business Accounts Business Lending
LOANS
LOAN TYPE
Rates Debt Consolidation Program Home Equity HVAC Mortgage Loans Personal Loans Secured Loans Vehicle Watercraft
Online
Home Banking Remote Deposit Bill Pay E-Statements PopMoney Virtual Lending Audio Response Payment Center Credit Card Payment Alert Me Check Reorder Overview
INSURANCE
Auto & Home Life Insurance AD&D / HAP Identity Theft Ins.
Help
Sitemap Bill Pay Instructions
Promotions
Promotions Six Flags Fiesta Texas
INFO
Our Story
About Us Leadership Community First Access All Stars Best Places to Work Commercials
Contact Us
Phone & Hours Locations Survey Employment
CONNECT
Blog Video Blog Newsletter Facebook President’s Report Annual Reports Bauer 5 Star Rating A.J. PerezScholarship
TOOLS
NOTICES
Fee Schedule Privacy Notice Complaints Notice to Members
HOME BANKING LOGIN
ENROLL NOW
NOTICESFee SchedulePrivacy NoticeComplaintsNotice to Members
Privacy Policy
NOTICE OF PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR CREDIT UNION MEMBERS
FACTS: WHAT DOES ACCESS COMMUNITY CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
WHY?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
WHAT?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
account balances and payment history
credit history and credit scores
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
HOW?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Access Community Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information:
Does Access CCU share?
Can you limit sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
Questions?
Call 806-353-9999 or 800-687-2990 or go to our website, www.accesscreditunion.com.Who we are
Who is providing this notice?Access Community Credit Union
ACCU is owned by its members and run by a board of directors you elect. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a top priority of this credit union.What we do
How does Access Community Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Access Community Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
pay your bills or apply for a loan
use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes- information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws may give you additional rights to limit sharing.Definitions
AffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
*Affinion Group is an Access Community Credit Union Affiliate.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
*Access Community Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
*Our joint marketing partners include advertising/marketing agencies, loan recapture programs, and financial advisers.Other important information:
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information.Download Privacy Notice with Opt Out Form
TODAY'S RATES
AUTO
As low as 1.99%
HOME EQUITY
As low as 4.50%
SIGNATURE
As low as 10.90%
MONEY MARKET
Monday & Friday: 9:00am - 5:30pm
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday:
9:00am - 5:00pm
Drive Thru Hours
Monday through Friday: 7:30am - 6:00pm
Saturday: 9:00am - 12:00 noon
2531 Paramount - 806.322.5020
6401 South Bell Street - 806.353.9999
201 Tascosa Road - 806.242.4444
accesscreditunion.com
Email: accesscu@accesscu.net
The website you have selected is an external one located on another server. We are offering the link for your convenience. Access Community CU has no responsibility for any external website. We cannot warranty, expressed or implied, any external site. Thank you for visiting our website. Click "OK" to continue or "Cancel" to go back.
Your savings federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government.
© Copyright
2018 by Access Community Credit Union. All Rights Reserved.
COMPLAINT RESOLUTION
SITEMAP
Access Community Credit Union is committed to serving all persons within our field of membership, including those with disabilities. We strive to make not only our physical branches accessible, but also to conform to WCAG 2.0 guidelines for website accessibility. Our efforts are ongoing including frequent testing and updates to improve accessibility. Should you have any problems accessing our branches or website, please call us at 1-800-687-2990 so that we may promptly assist you and remedy any accessibility concerns.
